So now we are going to peel our shrimp.
So we have some beautiful brown gulf shrimp here.
What I'm going to do this is the head is already off.
What I want to do is just go ahead and just put my thumb right there just on the bottom.
You kind of peel off this tip part layer of shell and at that point go ahead and hold pull on it like this.
Pinch this end of it and the shell would come right off.
So now you have a beautiful shrimp just like that.
So we are going to do this to our others.
Just go ahead and take that top part off.
You are going to make some really shrimp stock with this these shells so I encourage you we only have a few here but you can put them in a bag in the freezer.
Then you have enough accumulated you can make some shrimp stock.